Searching for Cannibal Holocaust is a documentary
film directed by Calum Waddell.
Italian horror fan and academic Calum Waddell speaks with some of the original makers of the controversial horror classic "Cannibal Holocaust" before
venturing into the Amazon jungle and surrounding city port, Leticia, to uncover some of the local stories behind the making of the motion picture.
What is uncovered, however, leads to a wider and unexpected "true crime" story.
Self, played by Calum Waddell.
Self, played by Carl Gabriel Yorke.
Self, played by Danilo Abadia.
Self, played by Madame Blanca.
Self, played by Ronaldo Blanca.
Self, played by Tara Chowning.
Slave of the Cannibal God (Italian title: La montagna del dio cannibale, literally The Mountain of the Cannibal God) is a 1978
Italian horror film starring Ursula Andress and Stacy Keach, with English dialogue, that was filmed in Sri Lanka.
The film was also widely released in the U.S.
in 1979 by New Line Cinema, and released in the U.K.
under the title Prisoner of the Cannibal God, with
a poster designed by Sam Peffer.
The film was banned in the U.K.
until 2001 for its graphic violence and considered a "video nasty."
The film explores themes of filmmaking, making of, amazon tribe.